through shadows, heart wrapped in chains, a mortal soul aching, tethered to pain, whispers
of a love she could never see, a hidden hand guiding her destiny, from the
I got a desire in shadows between Cupid's wings beating against fate's cruel wall
One spark, one touch, could ignite it all Forbidden fire, 11
Through trials and terror, the darkness they fight
Two hearts collided
In the edge of night, sight rise on wings of light
Love is a storm in the endless night
Through fire, through fear, through tears we climb
Eternal stars beyond space and time
I think it was skeptics and beautifully unhinged wanders of the internet.
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV, a place where chaos meets clarity and every voice is a
mirror of the collective dream.
I'm your host, Father Psyche the Cat Daddy, and tonight we're cracking open the vault
Out there, the panelverse is alive, trolls sharpening their claws, mystics, turning their
frequency, lovers, fighters, tricksters, prophets, all tangled up in the digital circus we call
home.
But in here we pause, we listen, we laugh, at the madness, and maybe just maybe learn
something about our own reflection.
And remember, no one leaves the psyche verse unchanged.
Let's awaken.
Okay.
Trying out some new features here.
Oh my gosh, my nose.
I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm big screen.
Let me put my comments on the screen
so I can see the comments.
Oh, hey guys, what's up? You need some hot cocoa? Uh-oh. Yeah, everyone.
What? I'm not actually like, hitting you, buddy.
I'm just having my beer. I'll be okay. I know I'll be okay. I'm always okay. I'm always...
Saki always wins, right?
Some good shit. Hurricane Punch.
A good type of wound in my head.
my hair is red excuse me yep excuse me you like a you like a redhead alex i'm trying
to try to please you mcqueen mcqueen bean
okay let me fix this up how is everyone doing we're not fun always having fun right
I like cute with shorter hair. Well, you know what the thing about hair is that you can cut it
That's getting long. I know long and unruly
Look, wait, you see me in the wig. That's even longer. But yeah, my hair is not bad. It's kind of it's not gray yet
That's my
Well, my beard is gray now. Look it's all turning gray. Let's go get a haircut anyone want to donate for that
I'll be happy to
Probably 30 30
Anyway
Cannot afford it right now
But it goes to here how much is the haircut over here? I'd say probably like 20 25 bucks
Let's see here, let me just risk it we're just gonna start it hold on
Yeah, because of me.
I love it.
Let her love shine
thousand scars. She carries them softly like the night hold stars. Tattooed maiden with fire in
her skin. Every battle she faced, she rose again. Sweet song, fierce and bright. Kentucky woman
with a lion's fight. She'll yell at me, but she'll make me smile. Sweet summer wall.
With grace every mile
Tattoo maiden with fire in her skin
Every battle she faced, she rose again
People are such jerks like half the people had to leave like in the last minute because I played that. I mean really
The people I don't want to hear anyway, they're just gonna leave I play a song that sweet summer
I mean really I've already drank most of my beer
Ready to get fucking drunk. Hey Chanel. Hey Alex. How are you guys?
People are such jerks
I mean geez welcome
Choking in the fucking but thank you guys for staying though. I mean it's like really like a two-minute song
Can't know let me just leave all goes to check in as well. The Hill Hill. Thanks. I'm interested in saying or else
I
Don't know
We just need a drunk putt pass out wake up at like 8 p.m. I go, oh, what did I do?
Hoof, it's like I would like to go to like a show and hang out and it's like
Where am I welcome right now probably careless Kate's Samans panel
Be this that I'm welcome I heard that she's never on
So, I mean, I haven't talked to be at all, like even when I've been in the same panel with her, she hasn't acknowledged me or saying anything to me so I don't understand like why it's like, oh, I'm trying to talk to and I haven't talked to her even.
I've talked to Alexandra more than I talked to beta in the last week.
Because it's like in my experience like no contact is like something you do to like punish narcissists. And so it's like
Cuz I'm not I
Don't know I
Know well
But it's not friendly there, it's like it's hardly friendly here, but it's like, you know, it is friendlier here than like a lot of places, but
know she had so that's that's as long as I haven't talked to I mean I haven't
spoken to beat in seven days I haven't spoken to her in 70 I mean I haven't
haven't spoken to her even longer so I understand it's like and I don't think I
ever tried to like make them friends but I do like want people to get along and
I think there have been misunderstandings maybe I don't know maybe
there haven't been maybe it's like everybody that's said things like said
I don't know so we all started as friends. It's kind of like I
met
Alexandra through like be to introduce or told alexandra about you know about me and like so we were all like good
I'm sorry, I shouldn't be like talking about people but uh, I
Don't I'm like in a state of confusion
I don't know if I'm like just not smart enough to like keep up with all this like
But I just wanted like people to like at least get along
But
Thank you Alex, it's okay to be sad. I know I'm but it's like I'm not even like I'm like should I be I'm like
I don't know what to feel. I'm just confused
So maybe that doesn't mean I have stuff to work through like psychologically or something, but I
Don't know it's like all of a sudden I I don't know I
Hear you I hear you. Well, I don't think some people are like
I'm not necessarily trying to play as my feelings, but I'm just kind of a mess, you know
And I'm sorry for people to have to deal with me like cuz
I'm not easy to deal with I'm not like even for myself. It's not easy for me to deal with being myself
It's like I'm a bundle of contradictions. I'm like a
Lot of things at the same time
Maybe I just feel like I don't want to
Inflict myself on people and
Maybe I have and I don't want to turn people against each other
I'm really about like really I really am about love like I'm a love
Okay, like a warrior for lovers like a I believe in it. I
like turning hate into love I like
Alchemizing, alchemy, alchemizing, like um, I like turning negative to positive, I like I don't know
Yeah, so that I just think I should just go away like just like leave everybody alone like I make many things worse
We're not talking about like going away. I'm trying to say oh, yeah, I'm like don't I can like live my life, but I
Don't want to be like more of a negative than a positive because all I'm trying to do is be a positive
In people's lives, and it's like
Well, I'm not then I'm failing and it's I don't like to fail
Restricts I'm Rudy's right here. Hello tricks. It's chicksies priests. He's running around
But I'm sorry, I'm like I'm not a good friend either. I'm not a good friend so I'm like so self-absorbed
I'm sorry if I'm not a good friend to people I'm sorry
Lola I see is Rudy
I'm drinking too fast. I'm drinking. I already have like hardly any of this left and I just I only have two and I just started
something at 5 p.m. I
Can drink it really quick I
Emotionally better with my art and music I don't even think so. I don't think she she doesn't like it. She's just like, oh
I mean, it's not gonna reach her heart, you know
Not gonna reach her heart. It's like it's just gonna go it's gonna hit her her her brain and then it's gonna she's gonna reject it
That's how it's gonna go
So don't worry about me trying to bait her or anything. She doesn't care. She doesn't care about me. She doesn't
And she like even if it seems like she does like she's like, you know, she's
She's faking it. She's like she's not she doesn't she doesn't care about me
Give up on I did give up on her like I didn't I don't think anything
Never gonna come I don't even think I'll ever meet her. I don't think she wants to meet me. I don't think
I'm gonna teach you likes me very much. I don't think she's ever liked me if you look at this like I always say like
like
Am I crazy or is she like talking about me here?
Am I crazier? She's talking about me. Just like watch
You sound like you slack I came through I told you again. I come through with a lyrical assassin
That's why I like to rap and attack you you sound wack. Are you from Cali? You don't even smoke on no bud
Talk about me
We got that brown word and oh geez we got golden girls on the homies
Listen bitch. This is how I rap. I get you cranked up. This is how I do it
I get people fucking vibing. I do like it. You did good
I did you want every day everybody give a W. I lost I'll take the L
But it was fun, right?
But now you can't even call me golden girl anymore because I won't I will call you golden girls till the end of the
Fucking day cuz you're on this panel for a psych and your mother fucking gay
Okay, he's gay
Bitch is fucking making me irate
Fuck you at man. I will go dyke if I stay on the panel for another motherfucking minute
Yo, shout out to chat yo, and let me tell y'all something
I'm always lit. He's quitting. You suck what her beat. Oh, it's
Wait, you know white person and this guy's black and she did a good job at fucking China battle with this like guy with a
Bird emoji and she took the W
Yeah
You lost though
I did. I won.
No, you lost. You took an L. You know what I'm saying?
You are the, like, miles ahead.
I mean, what are they talking about?
I mean, is it about them or is it about me?
Am I just being paranoid?
Oh, kisses, kisses.
Oh, you love kisses.
I mean, am I crazy, guys?
Look, listen to what they're saying.
Listen to what they say.
So so you can smell my rap got you fucking
If I can get you on the panel and I can get you riled up if I can get my fucking pussy ass
And I get you fucking cracked up. I'm good. Peace out West Coast
Where is Pikey at?
Let's see if he cracked us.
Bitch.
Oh my god.
Now she's talking about us.
So I wanted to rap battle you Trash.
All right.
I listened to her.
You Trash.
I wanted to rap battle.
There's nothing more to say.
Your shit is fucking like, it's like, it sounds like the same shit you're fucking
wrapped about every day.
I fucking cum and I fucking make motherfucking gay for our pay.
Okay?
What the fuck is that?
Correct come with the fucking like the current events talk with the fucking chat
Learn how to fucking yeah
Some wacky the ass fucking shit that you fucking wrap all the fucking time on every fucking panel
Show us how you fucking manhandle
Sorry
Lenore do you want to be the star of the show?
You want to be the star of the show?
You can be the star.
Why are your eyes so big?
Why are your eyes so big, my little kitty cat?
Hi, I'm the Norr.
Oh, you think when I sketch your ear, you're like, oh, like that?
Like that in your, in your, in your ear?
In your ear?
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
My baby, are you my baby babe?
You're my baby babe, isn't she beautiful? You're the cutest kitty
My little black my little black puss. Oh, you're winking
What she wanted
Hi
Hi, what what?
Hi kissing she gives me kisses
You're the star of the show Illinois, you know you're the star. You're so beautiful
She gives me kiss kisses. Are you happy? Yeah, you're happy kitty. Oh
There's a star and the star of the show means means everyone loves you the most
You'd like to hold her. I know she's the sweetest cat. Are you a sweetie heart? You're a sweetheart
What are you doing? She's purring. She's purring. You're happy cat, huh?
Your eyes like that your eyes are big
Jesus sweetheart, dear sweetheart. That's I'm like the luckiest guy cuz I got tricks. I got Rudy. I got Lenore. I got Lola
I got marbles sometimes. Oh, oh she kissed me
I love you
Jesus star
You're the star of the show. She's purring. Can you hear her purr? Here.
Oh. Can you hear her purring? I'm real pathetic, Bronzebird. I'm real pathetic.
Here, listen to your rapping. If you want to hear a pathetic, listen to Bronzebird rapping.
It's worse than fucking, you know, William Hung rapping. When he hears rapping, it's
Let's play it. Let's play the rapping
The hot dogs and shove it down your fucking throat one by one when you docks your fucking wife
You came up here and you fronted your own fucking wife. You fucking ice cream
I'm here bronzer Bronzeberg pathetic rapping me here at Bronzeberg pathetic rapping, please
The hod dogs and shove it down your fucking throat one by one
I'm not trying to say to my hot dogs and stuff. Hold on one second. I don't know why the there's a hot dog blind in there
Let's see. No, we look at the broads for trapping. Here we go
Of course you trash. So go ahead. All right. All right. I'm trash
I'm trash
But what who at least I'm not a fucking bird in the fucking sky a black one
And that's what I'm doing is the app and like a fucking bad one
Very
The way that you talk it doesn't even sound sick
He's raven and he looks like he needs a little bit of a savin
Yeah
So everything that you're saying is talking shit, but you're not sick every time you talk
You need to leave the stream and get high off your cat's cat in it. So when you're
I
Bronze chicken
Hold on
Hold on I'm right back bronze chicken stop your yapping
You want to come on the panel? I'll talk to bronze chicken. Get up here. Are you a little bit too much of a bronze pussy to come up here?
I'm mad. I'll come get on up here. I'll talk to you bronze chicken. You're not gonna over talk me on my show
Get up here. I'm not gonna say the n-word but
Nincum poop, okay
Bronze chicken are you gonna come no
He's not he's scared. He's too scared
Bronze chicken you have like 30 seconds to get up here
There's bronze chicken gonna come up here. We'll see. Let's see. We'll see who the real chicken is
Bronze chicken why don't I hear you on the panel you want to yap in the chat? Oh
Here he comes guys. He came he came here. Hold on
Where am I hold on I'm so sorry
What's what what's up? No, I just know why you so upset are you so mad? Why are you making 12 videos on me and beta?
What are you talking about?
You made 12 videos on me and Bita.
Those clips.
I did.
Oh, now you gas-laying me.
So now you playing stupid.
No.
So what was what was the objective of why you made those videos and then you made a caption talking about I'm racist and
Missed that in a third. What was the what was the videos that I made? No, I'm not talking about I'm not talking about that
I'm talking about those lame-ass videos you made about me
No, I don't need you to clip it
No, I don't want you I don't want you to play it
You still echoing
I'll be right back
That better no shit still echo to son
What I think about me is if I'm gonna talk shit, I'll pull the fuck up. That's one thing
Why are you mad at me in the first place?
Like why are you fucking you you are fucking
I'm gonna tell you why yeah, tell me you tell you why I tell you why
You're fucking deceiver and the thing about it is is when I called you dumbass out for manipulating beta you sat there and fucking lied about
So I can finish when I'm telling you
Go ahead finish
You're a deceiver
You don't have good intentions when you first made your panels you shit on your fucking friends
And then you sit up there and you play this game like you don't throw you don't throw rocks and throw you and hide your hands
Stop trying to play victim because you ain't scaring nobody and nobody believes you with that shit you talking about
You can do all that crying and all that emotional shit. We ain't fooled
You have PBD. That's what you have. You need to get a therapist
It is sick and demented the fact no matter that you obsess over me and beta as much as you do
What's your B&B? Are you a couple now? You're a couple now now we're friends your friends and you know, it's really ironic
Why'd you turn against me? You know, it's you know, it's really ironic. Why did you turn against me?
I'm more of a friend to be there than you ever have been
When she sat up there and told you to stop talking about her. You still made a video on her. That's first
Roll with Alexander you're a shitty friend
Alexander okay, Alexander, excuse me Monica Forster
They stood up there and Docs beat her and just like a boss for Monica, something else, Monica, something Monica force that that's what the fucking name is.
What's your last name guys, Monica, something else, not more forced to the foster.
Say you can you can play this game like you playing victim. You're not fooling nobody I pulled your card. You're a liar
You're a nice record. I want to hear my reading. You better than everybody because I
Better than everybody
If you've been on YouTube for over a year, I don't care you think what I did
You think you hot shit because you have more subs than me. I'm hot shit. You're cold diarrhea
So what you think you better than me because you have more subs than me your songs is trash
You're trash over every little thing that happens to you
Secky haters club, which is like now on the billboard is winning cuz he was crying. It's on the top 100
I'm not crying. Oh, look at your community post, bro. I've been one you sit up there crying out for your friends if I
If I leave guys
You just remember I was here. You're my friends on an AI song
And you haven't heard the second haters club song, bro. You making videos on me
I'm dead ass taking a vacation.
You made 12, 12 videos on me, bro.
I didn't, I did two streams.
I did two streams on you and that's it.
And you making videos on me.
Cause you're jealous.
You're jealous that I have a better friendship
would be better than you do.
That's why you're mad.
You're jealous.
Have you ever heard the song?
You're hella jealous, bro.
You're hella jealous.
Can I play the song, please?
I don't care about the song, bro.
Like, you're jealous.
Say you look good at the chicken. I don't want it. I don't want to hear this
What do you say I could play it? I don't want to hear this. That's not like that's not even when I'm talking about
Yeah, well, I'm sorry to be played as dumb-ass trash Chris games mad about Chris though
Tony's just full of it
Sleepy's gone sour, because bitter baggy again
Alexandra had my back, that's the real one to not pretend
Welcome to the Psyche Hairs Club, where the shell is capped up
Virgin Flores says, if there's years, fuck!
One club I've met, I'm not a part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
Raw chicken, pluck those feathers
Toss it in the pan, make it fried
All this noise you're making
Can't hide the hurt inside
They scream full or a spotlight
But the stage is all mine
And we have our justice chorus
That proves I'm doing fine
Welcome to the Psyche behavior's club
Where the shell is gathered up
Waiting for attention, thirst is stuck
One club I'm happy, I'm not a part of
Go hate yourself
Go hate yourselves
They're lame as hell, like a rerun show
Taking all their trauma, but it's over, Joe
So let me ask you how I'm I'm begging for attention. I don't need nothing from you. You're a clout chaser. I'm not I'm a clout chaser
But do I do?
All your enemies in the same
Videos bro, what are you talking about? Actually?
What are you talking? Oh you go on to actually what?
Falling asleep in the chat even the guests were falling asleep on your job. I'm sorry to say no, they wasn't that's why I know
That's why I know you're talking shit.
I have more views without you, bro.
Even your guests were falling asleep in your own show.
I'm such good 2,000 views, bro.
Fuck you talking about it.
It's OK.
I have a lot of live shows that have more views.
That's why I know you will lose it.
You care about numbers so much.
But then you get to complain.
But you get to complain when people talk about you.
Approaching a million views, bro.
That's what we're talking about.
About a million.
Sikey, do us a million.
Bronzeberg stays under 100,000.
Exactly.
That's why you talking shit about my page
when it comes to numbers.
Why?
I don't need nothing off you bro why do you try to get had lives that was more
using me doing views on you so what are you talking about why do you turn against
the bronze chicken I have I have a show right now that's 1.2k views that
doesn't have anything to do with you so what are you talking about I have I have
those I really need to go if I really need to cross chickens oh if
Need to cloud off for you, bro. I would have been something use you. I'm better than we can help each other
Hey guys
I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help me. I don't want you to help
No, psyche. I don't want your help. Let me explain it to you again in perfect English. I do not want your help
About my channel
Why did you get a tattoo of BKG on your chest?
It's a temporary insanity, but you know what now it stands for Barry and Kate crew
You got rejected by Bita and now you feel no, no, no, no, no. No, no. I'm not a show. I'm a lot of show
Borderline personality disorder you need a personality. I have a personality disorder. Yes, you do
Because you're a psycho you're a weirdo you're mentally unwell you're mentally unstable. That's what's wrong with you
You have never met Bita a day in your life, you have never met her in person, and you got a tattoo of her, an avatar.
Who are you calling a personality disorder? Okay, who do you say has one?
You. No, I don't.
You have a borderline personality disorder, you need to get that.
What do I have?
A borderline personality disorder.
Oh my god.
PPD, you need help.
Without pathetic you are you crying over a woman you ain't never mean in real life, bro. I met Alexander
Hey, man, Alexander this little pussy boy
Pussy
Know I didn't get a tattoo Vita. That's what I know I didn't do you got a tattoo like an idiot
Because you can't even get a tattoo because you're so
Is that the best you know what you get a tattoo on your butt you just can't show it on my you didn't you got a tattoo
You got a tattoo of a woman
Are you mad because you got rejected by her, you know, oh my gosh
Doctor
Mmm, oh my god, she talks herself. Are you she did? Oh, so you support that right?
Are you guys actually talking to the biggest retard on YouTube bronze chicken this cock sucker?
Alexander who's after a shot of streaming nobody went over there
I didn't start streaming motherfucker. I didn't start streaming my boy
I can see 30 pounds on my ice-coast. I'm not a loser like you. I'm not a loser like you motherfuckers
I don't take 10 years to get to one K like you
Shut up you crap fuck
Motherfucker
I'll be at your Brooklyn crib in two minutes. Shit. Shut up. Don't fuck up. Yo LES is live
That's where you belong and lose a bill with all the criminals motherfucker
Shut the fuck up
Fuck you bag it
I'm gonna die something so are you you don't bitch
We're all gonna die aren't we? Hey, bro. How are you gonna die bronzeberg sin of this computer?
You're gonna die in front of your computer of a heart attack cuz all you do is eat ham and so
We see now fat you are you fuck
Shut the fuck up
Alexandra mayors hate you Peter uses you for content and twisters your little mind your panel shit
and your
I want to be in your jealous that psyche has more viewers than you and subscribers. You just admitted it motherfucker
You just said oh
Why'd you get a tattoo a beat again
What's what's your business dickhead that you insane right and so when I say you possibly have borderline personality disorder
No, you're insane for caring. What is being assisted your mother? Why do you care so they were friends?
They are friends. That's why he got a tattoo because he's cool and one night
He woke up and got a tattoo. That's it. What do you care?
Why is your life so empty?
That's your only thing to ask psyche
Oh, I can't be friends with Peter desperate
Bronsford is the ultimate same jealous bitch and he stood up there co-signing that shit. What kind of friend is
Jamal Hendricks. Yeah, my name is Jamal Hendricks. Wow
Is it really one two three Sesame Street place in New York say the location correctly one two, three
Next officer the ground in the little apartment seven four nine Van Brunt Street Brooklyn, New York pussy hold on hold on
Is that your real address bro?
type it in
Hendricks
Seven holy shit. Yo, you guys are asking for it though. You like doxing, right? You let easy
Brunsberg fuck you because you let people dox on your panel
Yeah, I seen it. He meant people in the chat doxing away and you let it happen
My name is Jamal Hendrix. I live on 749 Van Brunt Street, Brooklyn, New York
I don't know if you're broke or broke or rich you haven't sent me a dollar. So how do I know?
You need money because you you that desperate for views you need money your mom Hendrix
Talking about bro
Everyone suck psyche steak
Oh, you're mad. All right. Thank you. Don't call people. You open the panel and people come and suck his dick
You know that the people that have come up here or that's for friends. It's not like you you mad cuz be today
when your mom Hendrix
Your mom Hendrix that is the most generic black name on the planet your mom
Now you gotta watch out for people in cars.
See?
You're my child now bronze birdie cuz people gonna be videotaping you like paparazzi. Okay, let them I don't care
I know you don't have to give them permission. They are it's a free country
You can ask Eli so now when you're next panel when Alexander mayors has 30 fucking
Thousand pictures of you and it's exposing you don't blame anybody
Mohandric you the one that said it unless that's a lie
Exposed your more Hendricks. Look me up now
is
the
You want to crash out bro? You want to crash out because Vita don't want to be cool with you, bro
Is that why you was crying all day?
Memberships bro
Memberships bro membership. Let me see
Melissa I do actually I do I love boxing. I love it
Do I have a 10 membership? I don't know if I have it. No, do I have any? I have zero? Oh, no, hold on. 25 members? Okay, hold on.
How many members do you have at Bondsburg, by the way? I just want to check.
You know, he's got like a thousand and half of them on me by the way
Oh, you're gonna buy little bronze birdie memberships, what a nice guy psyche
Oh, I hope I don't get it I hope I don't get but you gotta be subscribed to his channel to get the membership, right?
He was mad
Sucking be the stick every day. He's not even a man. This motherfucker doesn't care about his own channel
He just appeared like be the be the be the be the be the be the be the brainwashed you the persian spell has
Took an over your bronze bird ass. Let me tell you you just docked yourself
You know if you're fighting for beta
You should be worried about your dumb ass panel. I am worried about my panel
No, you're not you're here fighting psych about beta and doxing yourself. So you gone crazy
Like think about that look in the mirror and say, what have I just done? What am I doing with my life?
I'm on psyches panel crying defending beta who could give a fuck about you
Peter doesn't give a fuck about you and you're acting yourself. So obviously you have gone crazy
Okay, look at psyche crying like three to four streams straight. Oh, I'll try to be nice
Yeah, because you did the same to him
So you did it for a week to him
Borderline personality disorder we hate psyche four panels you an allied master. Oh, we're gonna send more newer
You did it to him for a week. So now you're crying cuz he did it back to you, bro
If you can't take it don't dish it out. So
I didn't know how do you know you don't know shit
You don't know nothing, bro. Stop trying to project shit and run average big narratives. I get a friend. You don't know nothing
about psyche nothing bro nothing you don't have friends in real life hold on we can say the same
thing about you brosford you don't have friends in real life yes i do brosford doesn't have friends
in real life he's on fat fucking brooklyn there's no friends in same shit don't fuck up do we know
brosford in reality no maybe you have 30 000 do we know psyche so that bullshit that here say she
Go back to TPP. We're you not welcome. Don't fuck up there. So go by the go back to where you belong in the loser panel
Let's run in New York. That's all that's left. That's the only place you can go now
Bitches nigga, look at you, but but oh pissed and shit like a little fat bitch behind a computer in broken
All right, the Jenkins or whatever you just said your name was Hawkins whatever black name. What was it again?
Like Tyrone Jenkins
my name is jimmy hendrix jimmy hendrix the guitar player then van van brookland new york
van brookland street brookland new york look me up jimmy hendrix that's not what you said before
bro you shouldn't be giving that out man i don't think you're in your right mind no i'm sorry
no he just said he's jimmy hendrix so he's lying dick because before it was like jamal warner it was
Yeah, so she's out there said that Jamal one two Sesame Street plays Jamal Hendrix seven four nine fan front
Jamal Hendrix. There we go. Oh, so it is Jimmy Hendrix Jamal Hendrix
I know but short for Jim so you aren't playing Jamal Hendrix
So you didn't have to Jim Hendrix the greatest guitar player that ever touched the guitar
Jamal not Jimmy
Jamal
How funny Jamal
I'm 264 pounds. Are you really? Yes. How tall are you?
Please be more than six foot five ten to sixty four
It's fucked. That's a fat fuck. That's almost j1 style j1 is like five two nine hundred pounds
264 pounds, that's a lot for the little heart man. You gotta go out there Brooklyn has a lot of walking space go on and walk take walk
Well, fuck off my belly bitch walk bro
Make it another year beat a beat a croak heart attack
Bronzeberg's fucking funerals tomorrow
Fuck up. Guess who's not showing up me psyche or beta?
Hendricks
Hendricks Hendricks, who's gonna bury you? Who's gonna pay for your funeral dick?
If you live in broken that means you're broke that means you're a broke black man on EBT
Why can't I be friends?
Why does everybody hate me?
Ah, Alexander Maynard doesn't like you.
That's what really hurts you.
That's why you're doing this, bro.
I'm not gonna give a fuck about some dumb prostitute.
Yeah, 100% you do.
She's not a dumb prostitute, bro.
What are you crazy?
She's a movie star, and that was like 30 years ago.
Okay, that's like saying that about summer like oh, so wait you're friends with summer
You just call accent your mayor don't prostitute because she was in the adult business 30 years ago
So you just call summer a dumb prostitute same thing my man cuz summer actually was a prostitute
She wasn't even a porn star that bitch was on the street sucking cock
She was on the street my man a street hooker
And that's your girl
So what are you gonna say now dick about Alexander mayors?
When you hang out with street hookers
That has more money than you'll ever have more balls more fucking
Talent in a little pinky then you're 264 fat ass will ever have bro, and I know that hurt you fat boy
I know that man. Shut up. What you
Shouldn't be sucking exiles dick right now
He is on all I'm guessing Alice running New Yorkers with the losers are yo psyche's running fam
You don't want to come up on a psyche's laughing his ass off dick. He just left you to the wolves
He just left you alone
He knows I needed a little nipple
You said that you was gonna run off right you was gonna run off because you couldn't captain
Captain half one has been flexing by the way for the past five minutes. They haven't noticed captain. I've noticed the guns my man
Look at captain you want you want to be in that choke hold my man
You fat fuck look at captain happen. You want those guns raining down on you brother, huh?
Keep it up. Keep it up. What about it? I love being fat
What the what the fuck do you really see the guns captain action the 24 inch pythons?
Do you want those wrapped around your neck just choking you out the life?
Because you're a gay out of your fat ass just squeaking the Oreos and the baloney out of you
fat ass because you're gay come on that's funny that's fucking funny anyway so
psyche out here thinking he's so tough and he's this dad and a third did that
about three to four streams begging for a friendship because he doesn't have
friends in real life
that's a reality I know I know I don't have any real friend and then you sit up there skinny as fuck sit up there and you're born as you're born as fucking streams and you're
already asking 32 people here right that that was like your peak when I was oh you're a locale that's a reality that why do you think people watch
But no, your channel is fun, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro
compared demographics, Bronzebird?
I even have a larger African-American.
So thank you for that.
You're black.
What about African-American, what?
I have a higher African-American women demographic
than you, and you're black.
My channel was catered towards black men.
So what the fuck are you talking about?
My channel, my channel is catered to anybody,
but like a lot of black women enjoy it.
The fuck out of here, dude. No one joined your bronzer. The only people that joined
12 and Chris cap
Because Jen and Alexander joined right no because no they enjoyed and they like me they don't like something about me
Disappeal it. They don't like you do
Oh, they don't they're just there is my friend. Yo, yo, psyche. You know where you went wrong. This is the reason I don't like you
I don't like you is because you claim this is about
Community building and all this other shit, but as soon as somebody makes a critique about you. It's all about how many
Shower you get drunk on your streams you see
You sit on your catnip, and then you have the nerve to talk. Oh my god. I said I'm catnip. Okay. Oh my god
You're not
About numbers and stats roll like when do you ever get to reality is actually about
Some point but it is a show it is like a you know because it's about numbers for you, right?
It's my noise, my job, so it is my numbers.
It's my job.
But you use that to shit on other people
that have a lower subscription to you than you.
You do
He doesn't promote your channel
Before you became a dick
That bitch ass motherfucker on the screen right now was talking shit about my channel for the last month stop with that bullshit
Your channel, I want you to succeed brawns
You are you a bitch ass motherfucker. I said it to you on the panel. Okay, you know what? You're a bc
LL a bronze chicken little lush
You were straight bitch, bro
And then and then you really thinking you saying something and really you not you the one that's crying
You the one that's sitting up there saying oh, I think I might leave and go to tiktok
Fuck got it
Get to mr. Beast
I've never seen a man guess what jealous about another man Bronzberg. You're a love a psych
I'm jealous of him. I have a totally different demographic from him. What is he?
More than me. I don't care Rosberg. I got you mad. Huh? No
These bro you make 12 videos on me and I caught you
You mad
Well, that's your loss, you idiot, because she's the best friend to have, you know?
Who said manure to your house, bro?
No, no, no, no, she's not. She's a washed up fucking porn star.
Oh, please, do you understand? She's a brilliant woman.
Fuck, I agree, bro.
Brilliant
Bronsburg you play yourself you can never come close to that woman, bro
Okay, you're just a loser in Brooklyn. That's an accomplished lady. Shut the fuck up loser
Beyond you just mad you just mad because I know you're a loser and you're a winner
He's mad cuz he's a winner and you're a loser
Why you mad
Are you mad? She don't want to be cool with you.
Yeah, Alex.
Is that Alexandra Doxher?
Alex, Alex.
I'm going to talk to Bronmer alone for a second.
But thank you, Alex.
I love you.
Here.
Bronmer.
Why are you mad? Why are you mad? Keep talking shit. Keep talking. Why are you mad bronze address me address me?
Respectfully, I'm gonna keep coming at you
Oh, keep coming at me, Bronze.
Oh, keep coming.
Keep coming.
I want more.
You want to have a conversation or what?
I want more of the Bronze chicken.
Please, more Bronze chicken.
My name is not Bronze chicken.
If you're going to address me, address me correctly.
I looked up the bird you were, and it said chicken.
It did.
Address me correctly.
That is the Bronze chicken.
You said you like the Bronze chicken.
Again, what is my name?
Address me correctly.
Jamal Hendrix?
What is my name?
Address me correctly.
Jamal Hendrix.
One two three Sesame Street place. Nice. My name is also the grouches. You can try this again. What is my name?
Hey, look, Bronzeberg look, there's your channel link. My mods are posted
I don't want you promoting me. Yes, he does. He needs guys. He's desperate for subscriber. He needs it.
Oh, see what I mean? This is this is you talking shit again about
You bro, that's what you don't seem to understand it's not about I want to give them to you
I want to give you I want you to have some I want you I don't want to promote my shit
I know I want I want I want because there's nobody talking except for some like old black guys say, oh, thank you
Bro, brother show, you know, it's not very great. Oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on
Hold on. Let's let's slow this. Let's slow this good Bill Cosby in your show. He's let's slow this all the way down
I'm taking let's slow this all the way down psyche. I don't think you want to go there with me
I don't want to do that. I'm there. I'm there. I want the race. I'm gonna get work. Thank you
How many subscribers you bought bro zero didn't you buy subscribers you bought a thousand
I was just mad because I did my shit organically. That's why you talk
It's human. I bought but I bought that many subscribers. You bought
Bro, I can't I can't help who gives subscribers to me, but here's how many I bought for you bought subscribers
zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero
You shut the fuck up and listen for one second. Okay, good. I
Don't give a fuck about sub count. I don't give a fuck about views. I did 1k on my
Like I said you keep talking about views and sub count again, I tell you every fucking
It's my job just a shitty job you working on
Hey, I'm making a thousand dollars a month on YouTube. How much are you making 7k?
I'm making over a thousand dollars a month on YouTube
Zero you're making a zero
I have a job in real life. You idiot. What do you I don't and I'm making more than you
You're really not making more to me. So shut the fuck up respectfully
Okay, respect. What are you talking about? You're gonna brag about being on YouTube making money against
You're upset the psyche has more something you
You have no
How I'm not anything you're bragging about working there. I'm making money to go there. I don't care. I don't care
Wait, you're sitting on me for having a nine to five that's crazy
I'm not nine or five. What is that eating McDonald's from nine or five?
255 pounds nine or five. Let me hear this one. What's your nine or five bronze bird?
I thought we was gonna have a one-on-one. You still have you had the one-on-one dick. I didn't even know I was back
Yo, you had this dickhead talk, okay? No, no, go ahead. Like like like bro every time you keep talking
You're proving my point every single time you talk. It's all about views for you, bro
It's never about
All this community shit you talking about in this panel verse thing you trying to come up
I don't want to be
I don't want to be involved in your shitty panel verse. You don't have to be you don't have to be it's everyone
That's in the panel versus gonna get thousands of subscribers. You're gonna be sitting there
I do more I do more promotion for other people than you ever have. What do you tell me?
I'm running you mother right now
Every time a person comes on my panel, I promote their page
Every time every day and who is this? What is this same Bronzeberg channel? Do you see it on the screen? Look?
Bronzeberg, subjective bronzeberg.
That's not even you that's promoting that.
That's fucking Nick that's promoting that shit.
What are you talking about, bro?
Did I delete him?
Did I delete Nick?
Did I say?
That's not what I'm saying.
Everyone, you are really a fucking moron.
You are really a fucking moron.
You are really a stupid right now.
Everyone, describe the Bronzeberg, please.
For subscribe to Bronzeberg, okay?
Like, bro, like, bro, your whole life is pathetic.
He's flattering.
Your whole life is pathetic, bro.
He means it.
You care that much about zero money for about two point seven K subs and I have one point one four
Okay, sobs. Wow. Wow. I don't even know your subscribers, but you are concerned about it. You know my
Time you make that you make that a point. I didn't even know how many there were you know exactly you don't have a community, bro
You just have
That's why you got Janet coming around. That's why you
That's why you have Alexander McQuiefe gunning for you and stuff like that. You don't have real friends
You know what I'm saying
You said that and then you talk about Chona because Chona bought you 1000 subs. You can
I have connections in real life. I don't need no fucking
KFC please tell me and the place to be
You need YouTube to save your life and pay your rent, you low life scum.
My rent is 8-4 for the rest of my life, bronze bird.
Because your parents, your dad, and your mom gave that to you, right?
Oh, please.
Because you ain't never know how to work hard for a living.
Look at that.
You are fucking SilverSpoon, baby.
That's the most you are.
I've been out of play gaming as five years old.
You are a SilverSpoon baby.
I have.
I'm gonna pay a crime of a bitch because you ain't never had to work for a living.
I was telling us we're McDonald's.
What the fuck out of here, dude?
the
You'll never be McQueen or come like I'm just the way that y'all forbid psyche on me. She's me on you one-on-one mother fucker
Oh, I know you go
I'm so much stronger than you
Not you're weak
Crying over a woman you've never met in your life G
You got a tattoo of her never explain why
But yeah, he's only gonna have summer. They're talking about Hankinsen
Well, so you lost it, okay
Bronsford has been screaming like a
What drugs do you take it so what did you do cuz that's not a blunt my man, you're not chilling and you know like a villain
You're on cocaine heroin or pills, brother
He out here crying. He's like, I'm really trying to be friends with her, but I can't be friends with her.
Oh, friends! Oh, friends! Oh, friends!
So, Bernie wants in the club. The Brons...
Yeah, I'm just saying, Bita, why do you hate me?
I can't take it. Brons, where are you?
You and Brons, where are you with?
You will never be Mr. Beast, bro.
Mr. Beast?
Who the fuck wants to be that dick?
Bring your ass up, you can't even speak English bring your ass up
That's ghetto shit
bring your ass up shut up dickhead you can't even speak proper english brooklyn boy so you're 264
pounds you live in brooklyn and you talk like a ghetto faggot bring your ass up shut up you're
sucking betas dick alexandria doesn't want to be your friend betas doesn't give a fuck about you
you're trying to talk over me blah blah blah blah blah sake is not even here bro
Sike is not here. It's main captain have fun. So forget about psyche address me address me now
Oh psyche why you ran? Oh psyche look at him
He's still obsessed with psyche like a little bitch cuz he knows he can't handle me and captain have fun
So it's all about psyche
I need sums you bag it. You're gonna get your subscribers from this relax. Okay, you get a little fucking cloud
But something's like his cock
All right, thank you
bag it
In the static of the night
I'm so beyond
He ran once you left he ran I know he was like a little puss and he calls me gay and he's being a little puss
You're just so welcome back a bronze chicken. I have nothing against you, okay
Bronze chicken that always made me laugh. Oh your name is Jamal
Malcolm Warner if your name is like yeah, I don't care. I don't care
Cut off with the music. Okay. I'm sorry guys. Thanks for being here. I know I drank the two beers
And now I'm too drunk to continue, but I want to take Alexander
Bronzeberg captain night brother more flex more flex before you go
Let's gonna see one more time
Cameron
We said we're gonna sit up straight. Yeah, you don't want these pythons coming for you bronze birdie
Yes, look at the sexy guys Wow
Okay, I'm sorry
Yeah, there you go. Oh the full the full eagle spread the eagle spread. I love it
There you go guys
Like I said, I don't play around peace editor. Thank you. Have kept it have fun. Thank you guys
I'll be back on later. Maybe okay
You guys are awesome. Thank you for my friends. Okay. Love you. He's having a brother
in the temples of night, golden wings glowed in the candlelight.
Crowds came running just to see the flame, but envy was the price of fame.
And now he stands where the echoes fall, with tarot in hand, hearing every call.
From praise to venom, in the same breath said,
burns gold, not red